Guide to the Seymour Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographs, 1859-1967; Series XVIII; 4'9.5" (12 boxes)
  - People
    - Seymour, Elizabeth Atwater: photograph album, 1912-1930, undated (Box 98, Folder 125)
    - Seymour, Elizabeth Atwater: loose photographs from album, 1928-1936, undated (Box 98, Folder 126)
    - Seymour, Elizabeth Atwater: North African scenes, 1944 (Box 98, Folder 127)
    - Seymour, Elizabeth Atwater: Phillips Gallery of Art paintings and exhibits, 1914-1916, undated (Box 98, Folder 128)
      See also: box 114, folder 7
      See also: box 109, folder 87
    - Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), Circa 1840, 1885 (Box 98, Folder 129)
    - Seymour, Gladys (Watkins), [1891, 1910-1925?], 1929 (Box 98, Folder 130)
      See also: box 96, folder 100-101
      See also: box 96, folder 96-98
    - Seymour, Gladys; (Watkins); Margery Jenks, 1910 (Box 98, Folder 131)
    - Seymour, Gladys (Watkins); Charles Seymour, Jr.; Elizabeth Atwater Seymour, 1914-1915 (Box 98, Folder 132)
    - Seymour, Gladys (Watkins); Elizabeth Atwater Seymour; Sarah (Seymour) Howard, [1924?] (Box 98, Folder 133)
    - Seymour, Gladys (Watkins); others, 1904, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 134)
    - Seymour, Gladys (Watkins); photograph album, [1901-1904?] (Box 99, Folder 135)
    - Seymour, Gladys (Watkins); loose photographs from album, [1901-1904?] (Box 99, Folder 136)
    - Seymour, Gladys (Watkins): photographs taken by?, [1906?] (Box 99, Folder 137)
    - Seymour, Maj. Henry (1764-1846), undated (Box 99, Folder 138)
      See also: box 114, folder 10-11
    - Seymour, Gov. Horatio (1810-1886), undated (Box 99, Folder 139)
    - Seymour, Mary (Ledyard), undated (Box 99, Folder 140)
    - Seymour, Nathan Perkins: portraits, 1862-1885, undated (Box 99, Folder 141-142)
      See also: box 112, folder 100-101
      See also: box 109, folder 89
    - Seymour, Nathan Perkins; Thomas Day Seymour, 1889 (Box 99, Folder 143)
    - Seymour, Sarah (Hitchcock), 1861-1915, undated (Box 99, Folder 144-145)
      See also: box 93, folder 41
      See also: box 91, folder 11
    - Seymour, Sarah (Hitchcock); classmates of, from Lake Erie Seminary: Kittie S. Arnold, Helen Murray, Lizzie J. Stowe, Marietta Williams, unidentified, 1867 (Box 100, Folder 146)
    - Seymour, Thomas Day, 1861 (Box 100, Folder 147)
      See also: box 99, folder 143
    - Seymour, Thomas Day: portraits, 1861-1894, undated (Box 100, Folder 148)
    - Seymour, Thomas Day: in Asia Minor, on board ship, 1903 (Box 100, Folder 149)
    - Seymour, Thomas Day; Charles Seymour (1843-1913), 1852 (Box 100, Folder 150)
    - Seymour, Thomas Day; Clara Hitchcock (Seymour) St. John; Elizabeth Day (Seymour) Angel, others, Circa 1900 (Box 100, Folder 151)
    - Seymour Family: group, 1929 (Box 100, Folder 152)
    - Talcott, R.G., 1862 (Box 100, Folder 153)
    - Tolles, Abbie O., undated (Box 100, Folder 154)
    - Tolles, Emma W., undated (Box 100, Folder 155)
    - Watkins, C. Law; others, undated (Box 100, Folder 156)
    - Watkins, Israel, undated (Box 100, Folder 157)
    - Watkins, Marie (Bader); Charles Seymour, Jr.; Elizabeth Atwater Seymour, undated (Box 100, Folder 158)
    - [Watkins, Thomas Hamer?], undated (Box 100, Folder 159)
    - Watkins, Thomas Hamer; Elizabeth (Law) Watkins; C.L. Frey; E.M. Frey; A.H. Christy; A.J. Christy; E.Y. Courseau; Rebekah Courseau; Helen M. Fuller; E.L. Fuller; Robert W. Davis, 1896 (Box 100, Folder 160)
    - [Watkins Family?], undated (Box 100, Folder 161)
      See also: box 109, folder 91
    - Watkins Family, undated (Box 101, Folder 162-163)
    - Williamson, Edith E., undated (Box 101, Folder 164)
    - Unidentified men [Yale students?], undated (Box 101, Folder 165)
    - Germans: Wilhelm Christ, Professor Teller, Windisch, Kaiser Wilhelm I, unidentified, 1882-1884 (Box 101, Folder 166)
    - Miscellaneous unidentified people, undated (Box 101, Folder 167-168)
  - Places
    - Doolittle, Laura Leggett (Seymour): photographs of her apartment, undated (Box 101, Folder 169)
    - Parsons, William Cheney: home, undated (Box 101, Folder 170)
    - Seymour, Charles: "Dawning Day," Chatham, Mass., 1916, undated (Box 101, Folder 171)
    - Seymour, Charles: scenes from Chatham, Mass., 1913, undated (Box 101, Folder 172-173)
    - Seymour, Charles: 127 Everit St., New Haven, undated (Box 102, Folder 174)
    - Seymour, Nathan Perkins: home in Hudson, Ohio, Circa 1863, undated (Box 102, Folder 175)
      See also: box 114, folder 12
    - Seymour, Thomas Day: homes at 112 College St., New Haven; 34 Hillhouse Ave., New Haven, 1895, undated (Box 102, Folder 176)
    - Houses: miscellaneous, 1897-1944, undated (Box 102, Folder 177)
    - King's College, Cambridge, Circa 1904, 1961 (Box 102, Folder 178)
      See also: box 109, folder 92
    - Switzerland: mountain, climbing, Circa 1904 (Box 102, Folder 178a)
    - Western Reserve Academy, Berry Pomeroy Castle, undated (Box 102, Folder 179)
    - [Choate School?], undated (Box 102, Folder 180)
    - Chateau d'Andelot, Noyon Cathedral, undated (Box 102, Folder 181)
    - New Haven Green, [ca 1890?] (Box 102, Folder 182)
    - Yale: Phelps Hall, undated (Box 102, Folder 183)
    - Yale: miscellaneous, undated (Box 102, Folder 184)
    - Family graves, undated (Box 102, Folder 185)
    - Unidentified places, undated (Box 102, Folder 186)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Seal of Thomas Seymour (1632-1712), undated (Box 102, Folder 187)
- Oversize and Undersize Material
  - I SEYMOUR FAMILY: GENERAL
    - Early Papers
      - Charles Seymour (1777-1852): from Nathan Perkins Seymour, 1841-1843 (Box 104, Folder 1-2)
      - Charles Seymour (1807-1886): from Nathan Perkins Seymour, 1843 (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - Thomas Seymour (1735-1829), 1766-1767 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Geneological Material
      - Seymour Family, undated (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - II NATHAN PERKINS SEYMOUR
    - Correspondence
      - Nathan Perkins Seymour: from Charles Seymour (1843-1913), 1868, undated (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - III ELIZABETH (DAY) SEYMOUR
    - Correspondence
      - Elizabeth (Day) Seymour: from Charles Seymour (1843-1913), 1867, 1877-1887 (Box 104, Folder 7-8)
  - IV DAY FAMILY
    - Printed Material
      - Memoir of Sarah (Day) Holley, [1865?] (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Legal Records
      - William Day, 1711-1769 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - VII THOMAS DAY SEYMOUR
    - Printed Material
      - Program from the inauguration of Arthur Twining Hadley as president of Yale, 1899 (Box 104, Folder 11)
      - Programs from the Yale bicentennial celebration, 1901 (Box 104, Folder 12)
      - Program from a performance of Hora Novissima, by Horatio Parker, 1901 (Box 104, Folder 13)
      - Yale Law School exercises program, 1905 (Box 104, Folder 14)
      - Harvard University Gazette, 1906 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Personal and Memorabilia
      - Adelphion Society of Western Reserve College: constitution, minutes, 1861-1867, undated (Box 104, Folder 16)
      - German universities, 1871-1872, undated (Box 104, Folder 17)
      - Passports, 1870, 1872, 1898 (Box 104, Folder 18)
      - Silliman house inventory, 1890 (Box 104, Folder 19)
      - Last will and testament, 1886 (Box 104, Folder 20)
      - Memorial, undated (Box 104, Folder 21)
  - XI CHARLES SEYMOUR (1885-1963)
    - Writings
      - Recollections of youth and childhood, undated (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Personal and Memorabilia
      - Wedding memorabilia, 1911 (Box 104, Folder 23)
      - Portraits of Charles and Gladys Seymour by John Angel, 1919 (Box 104, Folder 24)
      - Honorary Degree: Yale University, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 25)
      - Invitation, 1953 (Box 104, Folder 26)
    - Financial Records
      - Bank statements acct #31: Charles Seymour, 1948-1959 (Box 105, Folder 27-35)
      - Bonds Acct #31: Charles Seymour, 1949-1958 (Box 105, Folder 36-37)
      - Bank statements acct #32: Gladys (Watkins) Seymour, 1949-1959 (Box 106, Folder 38-44)
      - Bonds acct #32: Gladys (Watkins) Seymour, 1949-1957 (Box 106, Folder 45-46)
      - Bank statements acct #187: Charles Seymour, 1949-1959 (Box 106, Folder 47-50)
      - Bonds acct #187: Charles Seymour, 1949-1958 (Box 107, Folder 51-52)
      - Chatham "Dawning Day" and "White House" miscellaneous, undated (Box 107, Folder 53)
      - Estate, settlement of Charles Seymour's, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 54)
      - Estate of Kate Golden, 1908 (Box 107, Folder 55)
      - Income tax: calculations, 1943-1955 (Box 107, Folder 56)
      - Income tax: forms and correspondence, 1948-1953 (Box 107, Folder 57)
      - Insurance, [1940's] (Box 107, Folder 58)
      - Russell Trust Association: portraits, undated (Box 107, Folder 59)
  - XII GLADYS (WATKINS) SEYMOUR
    - Legal Records
      - Laura (Seymour) Doolittle estate: last will and testament, 1957 (Box 107, Folder 60)
  - XIII WATKINS - LAW FAMILIES
    - Personal and Memorabilia
      - Thomas H. Watkins: mortgage, 1884 (Box 107, Folder 61)
  - XIV CHARLES SEYMOUR, JR.
    - Writings
      - Books
        - Italian Quattrocento Sculpture: rough draft outline, undated (Box 107, Folder 62)
        - Italian Quattrocento Sculpture: credits for photographs and index, undated (Box 107, Folder 63)
        - Italian Quattrocento Sculpture: captions for illustrations in text, illustrations, undated (Box 107, Folder 64)
        - Michelangelo, The Sistine Chapel Ceiling: (Revision), 1971 (Box 107, Folder 65)
        - Jacopo Della Quercia: captions for plates, 1972 (Box 107, Folder 66)
      - Articles: published
        - The Choate News: article about King's College, Cambridge, 1931 (Box 107, Folder 67)
        - re: Nathan Perkins Seymour house in Hudson, Ohio, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 68)
        - "Vermeer and Camera Obscura:" original compilation, 1964 (Box 107, Folder 69)
        - "'Fatto Di Sua Mano," Another Look at the Fonte Gaia Drawing Fragment…", undated (Box 107, Folder 70)
        - Frick catalogue: introduction, undated (Box 107, Folder 71)
        - Book reviews, 1950-1974 (Box 107, Folder 72)
      - Articles: unpublished
        - "Democritas as Melancholy" [student paper], [1930's?] (Box 107, Folder 73)
        - "Identification of Three Ivories of the Metropolitan Museum," Aubert Focillon course, 1935 (Box 108, Folder 74)
      - Lectures
        - Sienna lecture, 1949 (Box 108, Folder 75)
    - C.R.I.A.
      - Exhibition catalogue introduction proof sheets, 1967 (Box 108, Folder 76)
  - XV ELIZABETH ATWATER SEYMOUR
    - Personal and Memorabilia
      - Last will and testament, estate material, 1962, 1969, undated (Box 108, Folder 77)
  - XVII LEGGETT - SEYMOUR - DOOLITTLE FAMILIES
    - Correspondence
      - Marilla (Wells) Leggett: from Leggett, Mortimer Dormer, 1862 (Box 108, Folder 78)
      - Marilla (Wells) Leggett: from Leggett, Wells Willner, 1862 (Box 108, Folder 79)
    - Personal And Memorabilia
      - Laura (Leggett) Doolittle: appraisal of contents of Thimble Farm, 1948 (Box 108, Folder 80)
  - XVIII PHOTOGRAPHS (oversize)
    - St. John, Clara (Seymour): Class of 1900, Bryn Mawr, undated (Box 109, Folder 81)
    - St. John, George and Clara, undated (Box 109, Folder 82)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1901, 1950's (Box 109, Folder 83-84)
    - Seymour, Charles, Jr., 1905-1906 (Box 109, Folder 85)
    - Seymour, Charles, Jr.: photograph of cathedral, undated (Box 109, Folder 86)
    - Seymour, Elizabeth Atwater: Phillips Gallery of Art paintings and motifs, undated (Box 109, Folder 87)
    - Seymour, Gladys Watkins; Elizabeth Atwater Seymour; Charles Seymour, Jr., undated (Box 109, Folder 88)
    - Seymour, Nathan Perkins, undated (Box 109, Folder 89)
    - Yale 1908 class reunion, undated (Box 109, Folder 90)
    - Watkins family, undated (Box 109, Folder 91)
    - Cambridge scenes, Circa 1903 (Box 109, Folder 92)
  - XVIII PHOTOGRAPHS (undersize)
    - Day, Thomas, 1861 (Box 110, Folder 93)
    - [Hitchcock, John?; Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour; Henry Hitchcock?], [ca 1856?] (Box 110, Folder 94)
    - St. John, Clara (Seymour), undated (Box 110, Folder 95)
    - Seymour, Charles (1777-1852), [1803?] (Box 110, Folder 96)
    - Seymour, Charles (1777-1852), undated (Box 111, Folder 97)
    - Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), 1854 (Box 111, Folder 98-99)
    - Seymour, Nathan Perkins, 1845 (Box 112, Folder 100-101)
    - Seymour, Thomas Day; Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour; Sarah (Seymour) Parsons; William Cheney Parsons, undated (Box 112, Folder 102)
    - Silhouette of Sarah (Coit) Day, [ca 1808?] (Box 112, Folder 103)
    - Miniature portrait in pastels of unidentified woman [Sarah (Coit) Day?], undated (Box 112, Folder 104)
    - Unidentified women, undated (Box 112, Folder 105-106)
    - Unidentified man (from the papers of Katharine Parsons Dean), undated (Box 112, Folder 107)
    - Unidentified miniature photographs, undated (Box 112, Folder 108)
    - Charles Seymour, Jr.; slides accompanying talk to Old Gentleman's Club, undated (Box 113, Folder 108)
  - I SEYMOUR FAMILY: GENERAL
    - Genealogical Material
      - Seymour Family, undated (Box 114, Folder 1-2)
      - Seymour, Charles (Folder 116)
      - Seymour, Edward, Duke of Somerset (Folder 116)
      - Seymour, Sir John (Folder 116)
      - Seymour, Richard, 1655 (Folder 116)
      - Seymour, Sarah Lowrey (Folder 116)
      - Seymour, Thomas D. (Folder 116)
      - Seymour-Devereux (Folder 117)
      - Baldwin, Harvey, 1807-1859 (Folder 117)
      - Howe, Mary Thompson (Folder 117)
      - Pedigree of Rashleigh (Folder 117)
      - The Woodbridge Record (Folder 117)
      - Pictures of ancestors, ancestral homes, coats of arms, etc. (Folder 118)
  - III ELIZABETH (DAY) SEYMOUR
    - Personal and Memorabilia
      - Certificates: Hartford Female Seminary, 1829, 1830, 1832 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - VII THOMAS DAY SEYMOUR
    - Printed Material
      - Richmond Daily Whig, 1865 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Personal and Memorabilia
      - Certificates
        - Western Reserve College: B.A.(1870), M.A.(1873) (Box 114, Folder 5)
        - Society of Colonial Wars, 1899 (Box 114, Folder 5)
        - Glasgow, University of: honorary degree, 1901 (Box 114, Folder 5)
        - International Congress of Archaeology, 1903 (Box 114, Folder 5)
        - American Philosophical Society, 1906 (Box 114, Folder 5)
        - Harvard University: honorary degree, 1906 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - XI CHARLES SEYMOUR (1885-1963)
    - Personal and Memorabilia
      - Certificates
        - High school diploma, 1901 (Box 114, Folder 6)
        - Trinity College: Ph.D., 1922 (Box 114, Folder 6)
        - Massachusetts Historical Society, 1938 (Box 114, Folder 6)
        - Columbia University: honorary degree, 1938 (Box 114, Folder 6)
        - Rollins College: honorary degree, 1939 (Box 114, Folder 6)
        - American Philosophical Society, 1939 (Box 114, Folder 6)
        - Pennsylvania, University of: honorary degree, 1940 (Box 114, Folder 6)
        - Paris, University of: honorary degree, 1946 (Box 114, Folder 6)
        - Lyon, University of: honorary degree, 1946 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - XVIII PHOTOGRAPHS
    - Angel, John and Elizabeth (Seymour): wedding portrait, 1915 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963)
      - Pencil drawing, 1950 (Box 114, Folder 8)
      - Portrait, undated (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Seymour, Elizabeth Atwater: paintings (from the Phillips Gallery of Art), undated (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Seymour, Gladys (Watkins): wedding pictures, 1911 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Seymour, Sir John: sarcophagus (1590), undated (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Seymour, Major Henry: silhouette, undated (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - [Seymour, Major Henry?]: silhouette, undated (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Seymour, Nathan Perkins: home in Hudson, Ohio, 1950, undated (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Watkins, Thomas Hamer; Charles Seymour, Jr.; Elizabeth Atwater Seymour, undated (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - General Leggett and staff, undated (Box 114, Folder 16)
- Additional Material, Accession 1982-M-010
  - ELIZABETH (DAY) SEYMOUR, Series III
    - Correspondence
      - Elizabeth (Day) Seymour from
        - Seymour, Sarah Melissa (Hitchcock), 1899 (Box 1, Folder 1)
        - Seymour, Thomas Day, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - DAY FAMILY, Series IV
    - Correspondence
      - Holley, Sarah (Day): from day, Thomas Mills, 1851 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CHARLES SEYMOUR (1843-1913), Series V
    - Indenture, 1869 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - PARSONS-DEAN FAMILIES, Series VI
    - Correspondence
      - Sarah (Seymour) Parsons: from Seymour, Sarah (Hitchcock), 1899 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Sarah (Seymour) Parsons: from Seymour, Thomas Day, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - THOMAS DAY SEYMOUR, Series VII
    - Correspondence
      - Thomas Day Seymour from
        - A-Z, unidentified, 1891, 1894 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        - Andrews, Catherine Augusta (Day), undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
        - Andrews, Katherine Elizabeth, 1892-1893 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        - Angel, Elizabeth Day (Seymour), 1892-1894, 1900 June-September, 1902 September - 1903 Mar, October-Nov, 1906 July-August (Box 2, Folder 10-19)
        - Day, Clive, 1894 (Box 2, Folder 20)
        - Day, Ellen (Pomeroy), undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
        - Day, Sarah Coit, 1877-1881 (Box 2, Folder 22)
        - Day, Thomas Mills, 1879-1887 (Box 2, Folder 23)
        - Ely, Charles Theodore, 1894 (Box 2, Folder 24)
        - Ely, Heman, 1880, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 25)
        - Ely, Mary Frances (Day), 1881, 1884, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 26)
        - Hale, Julia L., 1894 (Box 2, Folder 27)
        - Hitchcock, Clara Maria, 1883, 1886-1887 (Box 2, Folder 28)
        - Hitchcock, Herbert Allen, 1888-1890 (Box 2, Folder 29)
        - Holley, Sarah Coit (Day), 1880-1881, 1893, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
        - Jackson, John D., 1884 (Box 2, Folder 31)
        - Peabody, Annie (Putnam), 1881 (Box 2, Folder 32)
        - Putnam, Ellen Day, 1893-1894, undated (Box 2, Folder 33-34)
        - Putnam, Harriette (Day), 1882, 1893, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
        - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour), 1892-1894 (Box 2, Folder 36)
        - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour), 1896 September-1897 February (Box 2, Folder 37-41)
        - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour), 1897 March-May, 1898 May-August, October, 1899 January-May, October-Dec, 1900 February-August (Box 3, Folder 42-60)
        - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour), 1900 Sep, 1902 Nov, 1903 January-February, 1906 June-Nov, 1907 January-February (Box 4, Folder 61-68)
        - Seymour, Charles (1843-1913), 1888, 1892-1894 (Box 4, Folder 69-71)
        - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1892 (Box 4, Folder 72)
        - Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), 1879, 1892 (Box 4, Folder 73)
        - Seymour, Emily, undated (Box 4, Folder 74)
        - Seymour, Sarah (Hitchcock), 1892 July-Sep, 1893 July-Aug, 1894 April-July, 1903 January-February (Box 4, Folder 75-78)
        - Talcott, Mary Kingsbury, undated (Box 4, Folder 79)
        - Williamson, James DeLong, 1884-1887 (Box 4, Folder 80)
      - Bonaparte, Ellen Channing Day: from Annie Fields, undated (Box 4, Folder 81)
      - Peabody, Annie (Putnam): from Lucy Larcom, 1890 (Box 4, Folder 82)
      - Putnam, Harriette (Day): from Philip Brooks, 1890 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Writings
      - Published: books
        - The Family of the Rev. Jeremiah Day of New Preston, 1900 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Printed Material
      - 1908 January 8 (Box 4, Folder 85)
      - Yale University Commencement, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Personal and Miscellaneous
      - Autographs, undated (Box 4, Folder 87)
      - Title search, 1891 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - SARAH (HITCHCOCK) SEYMOUR, Series VIII
    - Correspondence
      - Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour from
        - Andrews, Catherine Augusta (Day), undated (Box 5, Folder 89)
        - Angel, Elizabeth Day (Seymour), 1896, 1902-1903, 1906 (Box 5, Folder 90-92)
        - Barrows, Laura L., 1863, 1865, 1878 (Box 5, Folder 93)
        - Braston, Mattie (Ladd), 1872, 1874, 1878 (Box 5, Folder 94)
        - Busa, Ella E., 1873-1874 (Box 5, Folder 95)
        - Day, Ellen (Pomeroy), 1882, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 96)
        - Ely, Mary Frances (Day), 1874 (Box 5, Folder 97)
        - Gilbert, Calla M., 1861-1864 (Box 5, Folder 98)
        - Hitchcock, Clara Maria, 1869, 1874, 1877-1879, 1882-1888, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 99-103)
        - Hitchcock, Clarissa (Ford), 1860, 1866-1868, 1874-1875, undated (Box 5, Folder 104-105)
        - Hitchcock, Elizabeth M., 1874 (Box 5, Folder 106)
        - Hitchcock, Herbert Allen, 1884, 1889-1890 (Box 5, Folder 107)
        - Hitchcock, Henry Lawrence, 1856, 1864-1869, 1872 (Box 5, Folder 108)
        - Hitchcock, Henry Valentine, 1863-1865, 1878 (Box 5, Folder 109)
        - Hitchcock, John Ford, 1862 (Box 5, Folder 110)
        - Holley, Sarah Coit (Day), 1874 (Box 5, Folder 111)
        - Parsons, Sarah (Seymour), 1902, 1906, undated (Box 5, Folder 112)
        - Putnam, Ellen Day, undated (Box 5, Folder 113)
        - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour), 1905, 1906 June-September, 1908 September-1909 July (Box 5, Folder 114-119)
        - St. John, George, 1906, 1909 (Box 5, Folder 120)
        - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1908-1909 (Box 5, Folder 121)
        - Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), 1874, 1892, undated (Box 5, Folder 122)
        - Seymour, Thomas Day, 1898-1906 (Box 5, Folder 123)
        - Wilbur, Philo A., 1878 (Box 5, Folder 124)
        - Williamson, Edith Day (Ely), 1874 (Box 5, Folder 125)
        - Unidentified, 1862-1884 (Box 5, Folder 126)
      - Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour to
        - Clara Maria Hitchcock, 1907 (Box 6, Folder 127)
        - Herbert Allen Hitchcock, 1888 (Box 6, Folder 128)
        - Mrs. Peck, 1903 (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - Printed Material
      - Hillhouse Avenue From 1809 to 1900, 1907 (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - Personal and Memorabilia
      - Calling cards, 1874 (Box 6, Folder 131)
      - Sketch of "C.H.S." (probably Clara (Hitchcock) Seymour), 1894 (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - Hitchcock Family Papers
      - Correspondence
        - Henry Lawrence Hitchcock to Hitchcock, Clara Maria, 1868 (Box 6, Folder 133)
        - Henry Lawrence Hitchcock to students of Western Reserve College, 1868 (Box 6, Folder 134)
        - John Ford Hitchcock to Hitchcock, Clarissa (Ford), 1861-1862 (Box 6, Folder 135)
        - John Ford Hitchcock to Hitchcock, Henry Lawrence, 1862 (Box 6, Folder 136)
        - John Ford Hitchcock to Hitchcock, Henry Valentine, 1861-1862 (Box 6, Folder 137)
        - Clara (Seymour) St. John to Clara Maria Hitchcock, 1906-1907 (Box 6, Folder 138)
        - Clara (Seymour) St. John to Clara Maria Hitchcock, 1932-1933 (Box 6, Folder 139-140)
      - Writings
        - Sermons: Henry Lawrence Hitchcock, 1843-1873 (Box 6, Folder 141)
      - Printed Material
        - Prof's Long's Inaugural Address, 1853 (Box 6, Folder 142)
        - Proceedings of the Triennial Congregational Convention, 1858 (Box 6, Folder 143)
        - Oration by Aaron F. Perry, 1867 (Box 6, Folder 144)
        - Catalogue, 1899 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - ELIZABETH DAY (SEYMOUR) ANGEL, Series IX
    - Correspondence
      - Elizabeth Day (Seymour) Angel from
        - A-Z, unidentified, 1885-1898, undated (Box 6, Folder 146)
        - Hitchcock, Clara Maria, 1885, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 147)
        - St. John, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour), 1903, 1906, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 148)
        - Seymour, Charles (1885-1963), 1897-1898 (Box 6, Folder 149)
        - Seymour, Elizabeth (Day), undated (Box 6, Folder 150)
        - Seymour, Sarah (Hitchcock), 1897-1908 (Box 6, Folder 151-152)
        - Seymour, Thomas Day, 1897-1899, 1906 (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - Printed Material
      - Program: Lake Erie College, 1902 (Box 6, Folder 154)
    - Personal and Memorabilia
      - Poetry: various handwritings, undated (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - ST. JOHN FAMILY, Series X
    - Correspondence